ANITA SISODIYA



WEB DEVELOPER



ABOUT ME

Passionate Frontend Developer with a knack for creating intuitive and high performing web applications. A result-driven and resourceful student with an interest in designing, development, requirements gathering and documentation who is always yearning to encounter new experiences and constantly learn.



CONTACT

Address:

New Delhi, Delhi

Mobile:

+91 9319134683

Email:

anitasisodiya1226@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anita-s-1225a01ba/

Github:

https://github.com/Annusisodiya



SKILLS

Web development

 ${\sf HTML}\,5, {\sf CSS}\,3, {\sf JavaScript}, {\sf jQuery}, {\sf JSON}, {\sf Ajax}\,{\sf etc}.$

Database

MySQL, Mongo.DB

Backend Technology

Node.js, Express.js

Framework

Material UI, React.js (Redux), react native

Software

Visual Studio Code, MySQL Workbench, MS - Word, PowerPoint



EXPERIENCES

FRONTEND DEVELOPER PS SOFTECH

2023 - 2024 Developed the same web application using REACT

Technologies

Developed and maintained responsive and dynamic

user interfaces using React.js

Utilized React Router for seamless navigation and to

enhance the overall user experience

MERN STACK NUMERIC INFOSYSTEM PRIVATE LIMITED

2022 - 2023 A pharmacy point of sale and management system web

application to manage medical store supplies, demand,

and sales

Technologies include React, tailwindcss, Redux, Contex-

tApi,

Node.js, MongoDB



EDUCATION

GRADUATION BACHELOR IN COMPUTER APPLICATION (BCA)

2019- 2022 Swami vivekanand subharti university (meerut)

DIPLOMA COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING

2018 - 2021 South point technical campus school of polytechnic



PROJECTS

PAYNRENT-BOOKING SYSTEM (WEB APPLICATION)

Car rental web application during my learning with basic designs.

• Interactive & User-Friendly Interface to help users rent for cars services and as per their interest, they can search category wise, subcategory wise and brand wise whether it is a CNG, Diesel, Petrol, Electric or any cars service availability.

GitHub Repositories - https://github.com/Annusisodiya/payrents

RESTAURANT TABLE BOOKING (WEB APPLICATION)

The project enables restaurants to order, create invoices, and share them with customers.

GitHub repository - https://github.com/Annusisodiya/restaurant.

PAYNRENT—APP (REACT NATIVE APP)

•These apps typically offer a range of features to make the process of renting a car convenient and efficient. Some well-known car rental apps include.